Guide to the Liberty Hyde Bailey papers, 1845-2004
Bailey, Liberty Hyde papers, 1845-2004
- Series XI. Honors and Awards, 1888-2004
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey Obituaries, Tributes, Remembrances 1954 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - "Liberty Hyde Bailey: An Appreciation" by George H.M. Lawrence 1955 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey Medal: Correspondence and photograph 1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Horticulture Stamp: stamps and newsclippings 1958 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Horticulture Stamp 1958 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bailey Centennial program and table setting key 1958 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Bailey Centennial description of photos 1958 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Bailey Centennial Kit: Pamphlets, etc. 1958 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Bailey Centennial Stamp, Newsclippings 1958 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Bailey Centennial Stamp first day covers and miscellany 1958 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Bailey Centennial Programs 1958 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Bailey's Centennial, Horticulture Stamp material 1958 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - "Resolution Commemorating the Centennial of the Birth of Dr. Liberty Hyde Bailey" 1958 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Bailey Birth site Dedication Pamphlet 1964 (Box 46, Folder 52)
  - Bailey Birth site Museum and Historical Marker 1964, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Liberty Hyde Bailey Birth site Museum Material June, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Tribute to L.H.B. booklet (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Series XII. Miscellany
  - Broadside for "How Plants Grow" lecture, 1879 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Ernest Gustavos Lodeman's class notes, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Miscellany, 1911 - 1985 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - "A Recitorial Address" signed by Andrew Carnegie to Liberty Hyde Bailey, 1912 (Box 46, Folder 51)
  - Junior Naturalist Club certificate signed by Liberty Hyde Bailey, Dec. 1901 (Folder MSS Box 41)
  - Pamphlets, 1940, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Bailey Miscellany (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Various printing blocks, including portraits and pages from journals (Box 66)
  - Printing block for the Loganberry illustration from "Gentes Herbarum", with page from the journal showing the illustration and a modern print, MU-2031 (Box 43)
  - Printing block illustration from volume V of "Gentes Herbarum", fig. 72, page 177, "Rubus Unanimus", MU-2376 (Box 71)
  - Printing block illustration from volume VI of "Gentes Herbarum", fig. 83, page 158, "Hedera Helix", MU-2377 (Box 71)
  - Printing block illustration from volume VI of "Gentes Herbarum", fig. 147, page 287, "Cucurbita Radicans", MU-2378 (Box 71)
  - Printing block illustration from volume VII of "Gentes Herbarum", fig. 159, page 250, "Spandis of Coco Thrinax Argentea", MU-2379 (Box 71)
  - Canvas collecting shoulder bag, MU-915 (Box 43)
  - Interview with Liberty Hyde Bailey, Edith Fox, and Jackson Towne, 11-6-1951; tr 8914
  - Bailey's camera, MU-255
  - Bailey's typewriter, MU-1184
  - m.225 (Folder MSS Box 12)
  - 150th anniversary poster, CD-506 (Box 20)
  - White cloth with signatures, 1917 (Folder 1)
  - Copies of plans of Bailey's house, 1899 (Folder 1)
  - 25th Wedding Anniversary certificate for Liberty Bailey and Annette Smith, 1908-06-06 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Signed by friends and family such as John and Anna Comstock and Mr. and Mrs. Mann
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Several items relating to Bailey including the Bailey plow are located in the College of Agriculture and Mann Library.